Leonardo Fonseca

UI Designer / Front-end

Bogotá, Colombia
cavera.de@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/leonardo-ui
portfolio-cavera.vercel.app
github.com/cavera

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I have more than ten years of experience designing user interfaces and interactions for e-learning courses for companies like Credicorp, Cencosud, and Banco Falabella. I'm passionate about technology. I can contribute my knowledge to the improvement of the user's experience. I enjoy the creative solution of problems, and I train myself constantly.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Head of design / Front-end

2016 - 2023

CrearMedia Perú, Lima - Remote

My specialization lies in UI design specifically tailored for e-learning courses. I focus on creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces that enhance the overall learning experience.

One of my responsibilities is leading a remote team of both freelance and in-house graphic designers. We work together to achieve successful outcomes on a wide range of e-learning projects.

Tech stack: Visual Studio Code, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Articulate Storyline, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Notion.

Senior Designer / Front-end / Tech Advisor 2012 - 2016

CrearMedia Perú, Lima

I actively participated in UI design and interaction design for e-learning courses, advocating for the adoption of HTML5 and responsive design as superior technologies over Adobe Flash. I provided technical support to clients and my team, ensuring smooth operations and efficient problem-solving. These responsibilities significantly contributed to the success and advancement of e-learning initiatives.

Tech stack: Adobe Flash, Adobe Photoshop, Visual Studio Code, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Trello.

Developer 2012 - 2012

CrearMedia Learning, Bogotá

I have actively supported the technical aspects and development of e-learning products utilizing Flash technology. Additionally, I had key role in creating and incorporating graphic elements into engaging e-learning courses.

Tech stack: Adobe Flash, Adobe InDesign.

EDUCATION

Corporación Nuestra Señora de las Mercedes 2002 - 2006 Professional Graphic Artist and Advertisement Technician

Platzi 2014 - 2023

Approved courses ans certifications: platzi.com/p/cavera_de

SKILLS

- · Self learner
- Collaboration
- Teamwork
- Adaptable

TECHNOLOGIES

- · HTMI
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- · React JS
- Figma
- · Sketch
- · Adobe Illustrator
- · GSAP
- ·GIT

LANGUAGES

- · Spanish (Native)
- · English (C1)

CERTIFICATIONS

- · JavaScript: Next Steps (link)
- · English Dot Works 9 (link)
- HackerRank JavaScript (Basic) Certificate (<u>link</u>)
- HackerRank CSS Certificate (link)
- EF SET **English** Certificate (C2 Proficient) (<u>link</u>)

SKILL TESTS

 UXCEL Verified Designer Assessment report (link)